(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-30T21:26:55.481355",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ
ATTENTION: To All Visitors
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ
ATTENTION: To All Visitors
秘密結社holoX Live 2026 「First Mission」
[hololive 2026 'First Mission' - Waiting Screen]
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
アニメにハマって
I got so hooked on anime
歌いたくなっちゃった
that I just had to sing!
推しのシーン見ながら
Singing karaoke while watching
カラオケ歌えるなんて…
my favorite scenes...
尊すぎてツラいっ！
...is almost too precious to handle!
歌いたいアニメ・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Find the anime and game songs you want to sing!
どアニメ宣言！ JOYSOUND
Super Anime Proclamation! JOYSOUND
本日は
Today...
秘密結社holoX 1st LIVE 2026 First Missionにご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to Secret Society holoX 1st LIVE 2026 First Mission!
自己紹介！
Self-introductions!
刮目せよ！
Pay attention!
我が輩の名前は、ラプラス・ダークネスだ！
My name is Laplus Darkness!
皆さん、待った？
Did you all wait?
holoXの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイと申します！
I am Takane Lui, executive officer of holoX!
みんな、こんこよー！
Everyone, konkoyo~!
holoXの頭脳、博衣こよりだよー！
I am Hakui Koyori, the brain of holoX!
ござるさんー！
Gozaru-san~!
喝！
Katsu!
おー、よく出来たなー！
Oh, well done!
holoXの用心棒、風真いろはでござる！
I am Kazama Iroha, the bodyguard of holoX!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます！
To ensure you enjoy the concert to the fullest, we have a few announcements!
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機器の使用は固くお断りいたします！
Photography, audio, and video recording during the show are strictly prohibited!
万が一具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください！
If you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and inform a nearby staff member!
いい子です！
Good child!
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージにものを投げ込むなど、他のみんなの迷惑になったり公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です！
Moshing, diving, excessive jumping, and throwing objects onto the stage are strictly prohibited!
また、3階と4階の最前列席は危険防止のため立ち見禁止です！
Also, standing in the front row seats on the 3rd and 4th floors is prohibited for safety!
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
お守りいただけない場合、ご退場いただく可能性がございます！
If you do not comply, you may be asked to leave!
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます！
Also, cameras for video streaming and photography are present, so the audience may be filmed!
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください！
Please note that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes!
いい返事だな！
Good response!
また、ライブのハッシュタグは #SSholoX世界リペイント計画 です！
Also, the live hashtag is #SSholoX世界リペイント計画!
ハッシュタグを使って、たくさん盛り上げてください！
Please use the hashtag to build up the hype!
それでは、開演までもう少しです！
Now then, it's almost time for the show to start!
みんなで一緒に盛り上がるでござる！
Let's all get excited together de gozaru!
みんな、静かに、静かに…
Everyone, quiet, quiet...
holoX LOVE!!! こよちゃん大好き！
holoX LOVE!!! I love Koyo-chan!
推しに感謝
Grateful for my fave
こよクロは永久
KoyoKuro is forever
こよりが一番
Koyori is number one
我等、エデンの星を統べる者
We are those who rule the star of Eden,
秘密結社 holoX！
Secret Society holoX!
時は熟した！
The time has come!
宵闇より現れし 愚民たちよ！
You fools who appeared from the twilight!
準備はいいかー！
Are you ready?!
Are you ready?
ラッパッパ ラッパラパラッパッパ ラッパタラッパタラッパッパ
Rap-pa-pa, rap-pa-ra-pa-rap-pa-pa, rap-pa-ta-rap-pa-ta-rap-pa-pa
夜が深まる ほら Darkness
Night deepens, look, Darkness.
脳内手持ちのウェポンで隠す
Hiding with weapons kept in mind.
何したってええと異議
Objecting that whatever we do is fine,
ノットニンニン サムライガール
Not Nin-Nin, Samurai Girl.
読みきれないけど
I can't fully read it, but
フルスロットルで粛清 粛清
Purging at full throttle!
開口一番
First word out of our mouths,
ザックザク
Slicing away!
悪の手のひら
In the palm of evil's hand,
踊りたくなる
It makes you want to dance.
ほら君も
Look, you too,
気づけばノリノリです
Before you know it, you're getting into the groove.
どうしようもない 運命だけど
It's a helpless fate, but
なんだかんだしょうがない
One way or another, it is what it is,
もう全部塗り替えよう
Let me repaint everything already!
XとXとXとXが
As X, X, X, and X
交差する真ん中で
Intersect right in the center,
NEXTとNEXTとNEXT
NEXT, NEXT, and NEXT,
世界はもう始まっている
The world has already begun.
Woah-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
飛び出そう 神が呼ぶほうへ
Let's leap out towards where god is calling!
Woah-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
暗転の暗黒 Xです
Pitch-black darkness, it's X.
混沌としたこの世界を
This chaotic world...
我ら holoX 色に塗り替えるのだ！
We shall repaint it in the colors of holoX!
皆の者、かかれー！
Everyone, attack--!
YES MY DARK!
アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ！
Absolute Darkness Infinity!
エデンの星は我が手中に！
The star of Eden is in my hands!
ラッパッパッパ...
Rap-pa-pa-pa...
風穴あけたんだ
Blasted a hole through it,
支配は始まった
The reign has begun.
息はもう掛けたの
I've already laid my breath on it,
バーチャルの資格ないはずよ
You shouldn't be qualified for the virtual world.
抑えきれない 自力制御不能なパワー
Uncontrollable power that I can't hold back myself!
捕まえてみなよ 影形もない My heart
Just try and catch it, my heart with no shadow or shape!
半信半疑な素振りは No, no
Half-hearted, doubtful attitude is No, no!
心に従って
Follow your heart,
忠誠心見せてよ 今こそ
Show your loyalty, right here and now!
Baby, don't let me down
ラッパッパッパ...
Rap-pa-pa-pa...
カラクリ仕掛けになるでしょう
It'll probably turn into a trick mechanism.
ラッパッパッパ...
Rap-pa-pa-pa...
並ぶ人足りてないのよ
There aren't enough people lining up!
Yes! ギフテッドなジェネレーション
Yes! A gifted generation!
革命的存在を
A revolutionary existence...
It's プレシャス 重大感情
It's precious, major emotions!
吹き去って
Blowing away,
ラッパッパッパ...
Rap-pa-pa-pa...
Darkness...
まだまだ行こうー！
Let's keep going!
「我が輩…」
"'Wagahai...'"
じゃない！
Just kidding!
お前もホロックスの一員となるのだ！
You too shall become a member of holoX!
Someone
to watch over me
Do you remember me?
しゃもじの面と面が合ったらきっと
If the flat sides of the rice paddles touch, surely
グラグラッタ
wobbling and rattling,
Nightmare
a nightmare...
ママ買っちゃった
Mom bought it,
それは WINK, WINK, WINK
that is a WINK, WINK, WINK!
でもずっとライアー ファンタジー マイタイプの目 WINK
But forever a liar, fantasy, my type of eyes—WINK!
ちょっと目がデカい 目に入れたって痛くないくらい
Your eyes are a bit big, so precious I wouldn't mind them in my eye
ラララ 口直しに Sweet pictures
La-la-la, sweet pictures as a palate cleanser
憎しみは特にとっ散らかった
Hatred was especially scattered all around
怖がってんの？
Are you scared?
ふ〜ん あっそう
Hmm, I see.
Don't let me down
まだまだ
Not yet, not yet!
安全じゃないかな
Isn't it safe?
危険じゃないかな
Isn't it dangerous?
それかなんだ
Or what is it,
フロンティア
frontier?
目には目を
An eye for an eye,
WINK シェラララ
WINK sherarara
見せ掛けだけ キミへ WINK
Just for show, a WINK to you
シェラララ やまなかった
Sherarara, it didn't stop,
愛 愛 愛 Want you で バイバイさ
love, love, love, saying bye-bye with "Want you"
目にも留まらぬ EYE, EYE
Faster than the eye can see, EYE, EYE
いいよ
That's fine,
目を瞑る半分ね まっ赤な WINK
closing half an eye, a deep red WINK!
まっ赤な
Deep red
まっ赤な まっ赤な
Deep red, deep red
真っ暗になっていく前に
Before everything turns pitch black,
合図だよ WINK
here's the signal, WINK!
WINK WINK... EYE EYE EYE
これにて一件落着〜！
Case closed!
これで君もこよにメロメロ〜！
Now you're totally head over heels for Koyo~!
みんなの脳みそに注射しちゃうぞ〜！
I'm gonna give all your brains an injection~!
実験だ！実験だ！実験実験実験だ！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment! Experiment, experiment, experiment!
実験だ！実験だ！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment!
一緒に！
Together now!
実験だ！実験だ！実験実験実験だ！実験だ！実験だ！実験だ！
It's an experiment! Experiment, experiment! Experiment!
研究！研究！研究！研究！研究！助手っ子呼ばれてピピッとポン！
Research! Research! Research! Called by the assistants, pipitto-pon!
検証！検証！検証！単純明快
Verification! Verification! Verification! Simple and clear,
舐めてたら火傷しちゃうよ！
if you underestimate me, you'll get burned!
迷った？ダメダメ 迷ったらサイエンス 迷走中？妄想はマヨマヨチュッチュ！
Lost? No, no! If you're lost, turn to science! Straying? Delusions go mayo-mayo-chu-chu!
今夜のデザート 今夜はハッピー
Tonight's dessert, happy tonight!
今夜に今夜に抱かれ恋焦がれ
Embraced by tonight, yearning for love!
サイン コサイン タンジェント 刺激的感度 敏感ダイレクト 特異な変異 新型カンパニー
Sine, cosine, tangent! Stimulating sensitivity, sensitive direct! Peculiar mutation, new-type company!
天才 天才 天才 とんでもなくエラい はぐれちゃダメ！OK？
Genius, genius, genius! Incredibly great! Don't stray away, okay?
ハメ外すタイミング 最高 最高 最高 飛んで回って優勝
Time to let loose, best, best, best! Flying, spinning, total victory!
ぶっちゃけ脳内シュワシュワ 炭酸ビッグバン！
Honestly, my brain is fizzing—a carbonated Big Bang!
科学とは 探求とは
What is science? What is inquiry?
バハッとポジティブ ポン！間違い pools ドジったとこも計算通りよ！
Bursting positive! Blundering mistake pools, even my blunders are all calculated!
実験だ！実験だ！実験実験実験だ！実験だ！実験だ！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment! Experiment, experiment, experiment!
実験だ！実験だ！実験実験実験だ！実験だ！実験だ！実験だ！
It's an experiment! Experiment, experiment! Experiment, experiment, experiment!
さあさあ もっと声出せるよね！
Come on, you can make more noise than that!
じゃあ 一緒に「実験だー！」って叫ぶよ〜！
Alright, let's shout "It's an experiment!" together~!
せーの！「実験だー！」
Ready, set... "It's an experiment!"
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
もう一回「実験だー！」行くよ〜！
One more time, "It's an experiment!" Here we go~!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
せーの！「実験だー！」ありがとー！
Ready, set... "It's an experiment!" Thank you~!
拙者、風真いろは！
This one is Kazama Iroha!
一刀両断！
Severing in a single strike!
たたき切れ！
Strike them down!
愛のネタバレ「別れ」っぽいな
Love's spoiler, seems like "breakup"
人生のネタバレ「死ぬ」っぽいな
Life's spoiler, seems like "dying"
なにそれ意味深でかっこいいじゃん...
What's that? It's profound and cool, isn't it...
それっぽい単語集で踊ってんんだ 失敬
Dancing to a collection of words like that, how rude
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる 風
Tu-tu-ru tu-tu-ru style
ぽいじゃん ぽいじゃん
Seems like it, seems like it
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる 風
Tu-tu-ru tu-tu-ru style
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる
Tu-tu-ru tu-tu-ru
神っぽいな
Seems like a god
もういいぜ もういいぜ それ
That's enough, that's enough, that
もういいぜ もういいぜ 逆に興奮してきたなあ
That's enough, that's enough, I've started to get excited instead
おっきいね おっきいね 夢
It's big, it's big, the dream
おっきいね おっきいね 景気いいけど品性はTHE END
It's big, it's big, prosperous but character is THE END
うええい うええい
Yeah, yeah
「Gott ist tot」
"Gott ist tot"
神っぽいな それ 卑怯
Seems like a god, that's cowardly
神っぽいな それ 「My God」
Seems like a god, that "My God"
アイウォンチュー ウォンチュー IQが下がっていく感じ
I want you, want you, feeling like my IQ is dropping
邪心っぽいな それ 結局
Seems like an evil heart, that's after all
邪心っぽいな それ 「My God」
Seems like an evil heart, that "My God"
アイヘイツュー ヘイツュー 害虫はどっち
I hate you, hate you, which one is the pest?
その髪型 その目 その口元
That hairstyle, those eyes, that mouth
その香水 その服 そのメイク
That perfume, those clothes, that makeup
アレッっぽいな それ 比喩
Seems like that, that's comparing
アレッっぽいな それ
Seems like that, that
その名言 その意見 その批評
That famous quote, that opinion, that criticism
そのカリスマ そのギャグ そのセンス
That charisma, that gag, that sense
神っぽいな それ 卑怯
Seems like a god, that's cowardly
っぽいな っぽいな っぽい
Seems like, seems like, seems like
憧れちゃう！
I admire it!
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる 風
Tu-tu-ru tu-tu-ru style
ぽいじゃん ぽいじゃん
Seems like it, seems like it
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる 風
Tu-tu-ru tu-tu-ru style
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる
Tu-tu-ru tu-tu-ru
神っぽいな
Seems like a god
どうしようもない どうしようもない 混じっていく
Can't be helped, can't be helped, blending together
目眩ましがない
There's no distraction
もう全部 塗り替えよ
Re-paint everything already
刮目せよ！
Pay attention!
エックスと エックスと エックスが
X and X and X...
交差する真ん中で
Right where they intersect
ネクスト ネクスト ネクスト
Next, next, next
世界は今始まってる
The world is beginning right now
ジャン！
Ta-da!
Woah-oh-oh-oh-oh
コピーな コンプリな 留まりたいドリーム
Copy, complete, a dream that wants to stay
Woah-oh-oh-oh-oh
笑うのわ 滅ぼして
Destroying the ones who laugh
ラパッパ ラパダパダパッパ ラパタラパタラパッパ
Lapappa lapadapadapappa lapatarapatarapappa
イエーイ！
Yay!
holoXのライブが始まったぞー！
holoX's live concert has started!
こんにぎわー！
Konnigiwa!
秘密結社holoXです！
We are Secret Society holoX!
全然秘匿性のない秘密結社...
A secret society with zero secrecy...
自己紹介するぞ！
Let's introduce ourselves!
さあ！狂気の宴の始まりだー！
Now, let the crazy feast begin!
貴様ら、刮目せよ！
You bastards, pay attention!
吾輩の御名はラプラス・ダークネスだー！
My name is La+ Darknesss!
はい、みなさん、まったー？
Alright, everyone, did you wait?
ふふ、新しいのよー。やってくれた、みんな。
Hehe, it's a new one~ Everyone did it for me.
holoXの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイと申しまーす！
I am Takane Lui, the executive officer of holoX!
まった？まった？
Did you wait? Did you wait?
はい！ちょっと新しいの行きますよ。
Yes! I'm gonna try a slightly new one.
あの小やりー！その小やりー！
That Koyori! This Koyori!
いけてるじゃーん！すごーい！
That went well! Amazing!
ありがとう！初めてやりましたー！
Thank you! It's my first time doing it!
holoXの頭脳、博衣こよりだよー！
I'm Hakui Koyori, the brain of holoX!
お前たち、わかってるよね？わかってるよね？
You guys know it, right? You know it, right?
いくよー？
Here we go!
ござるさんはー？
Gozaru-san is...?
あ、holoX？あ、ごめんごめん。
Ah, holoX? Ah, sorry, sorry.
ござるさんはー？
Gozaru-san is...?
あ、なんか内部の人間が変なこと言ってますが、holoXのイケメン強強カッコいい用心棒、侍の風真いろはでござるー！
Ah, internal personnel are saying weird stuff, but I am the cool, strong, handsome bodyguard of holoX, the samurai Kazama Iroha de gozaru!
ついにこの日が来てしまった…
Finally, this day has come...
始まっちゃった！
It's started!
見せられなかった！
We couldn't show it!
危ない危ない！
That was close!
最初のメドレーすごかったでしょ！
The first medley was amazing, right?
みんなこんな風に混ざってソロ来て予想できてた？
Did everyone expect it to be mixed up like this with the solos?
予想外～
Unexpected!
もう最初からクライマックス！
It's already the climax right from the start!
盛り上がりでもう... 始まったばっかだけどね！
With all this excitement... even though it's just started!
始まったばっかといえばさ、みんなあの自己紹介の時に実はみんなもうちょっとうるっと来てて...
Speaking of just starting, during the introductions, everyone was actually getting a bit teary-eyed...
その話は！
Don't bring that up!
楽屋の時点でルイさんは...
Even back in the dressing room, Lui-san was...
一番早かったのはルイさん！
Lui-san was the earliest!
いつも！いつもルイからじゃない！
It's always! It doesn't always start with Lui!
違うの！違うの！
No, it's not! No, it's not!
花粉症？
Hay fever?
ごまかすな！/ ごまかせないですよ！
Don't play it off! / You can't fool us!
いいじゃん素直に「メンバー大好き」って言ったって！
Why not just honestly say "I love the members"?
やめてよ！恥ずかしい！
Stop it! It's embarrassing!
それをさ、みんなでこういじってたのに...
And we were all teasing her about it...
ここ来てみんなの笑顔を見たらさ、ちょっとみんなうるっと来ちゃって...
But coming out here and seeing everyone's smiles, we all got a bit teary-eyed...
始まる前はさ、みんななんかもうこんなんで待ってたのに...
Before it started, everyone was waiting like this...
自己紹介始まった瞬間、めっちゃ笑顔になって...
The moment introductions started, everyone had huge smiles...
みんなのね、なんか声とか音とかがすごくて、みんな泣いてた！
Everyone's cheers and noise were so amazing, everyone was crying!
そう！うるっと来て、でも「やらなきゃ！」ってやったんだよね！
Yeah! We got teary-eyed, but were like "We gotta do this!" and did it!
やらないといけないよね！
We have to do this!
もう今日はかまさないといけないよね！
We gotta crush it today!
でも1曲目はかませたんじゃないか？かませてたー？
But didn't we crush the first song? Did we crush it?
ちょっとさ、最初の曲のメドレーのさ、タイトル言っといてよ！
Hey, say the title of that first medley!
ちょっと待って！これ読める？かっこよく言えるよ！
Wait a sec! Can you read this? I can say it coolly!
頼むわ！代表して！お願いします！
Please! On our behalf! Please!
みんな、場内X（旧Twitter）でみんな知ってるよね！
Everyone knows from X (formerly Twitter) in the venue, right?
今日のための特別タイトルあんだから！
There's a special title for today!
そうなのよ！件名だから！
That's right! Because it's a subject line!
いくぜ！
Here I go!
場内X（旧Twitter） Extended Remix みんなの必殺技詰め込んでみましたバージョン！
Venue X (formerly Twitter) Extended Remix: Packed with Everyone's Special Moves Version!
そのまんまなのよ！無理やりじゃない？
It's so literal! Isn't that forced?
かっけー！決まったぜ！
So cool! Nailed it!
配信組も盛り上がってますかー？
Is the streaming audience hyped up too?
配信カメラあるよー！
There's the streaming camera!
前おいでよ、前！
Come to the front!
コメントも見えてるからね！「イエーイ」「ウオー」しか言ってない！
We can see the comments too! They're only saying "Yay" and "Woah"!
「タイトル長い」って言われた！
They said "The title is too long"!
長くない！そのまんまなの！
It's not long! It's just as it is!
吾輩の名前より短いやん！
It's shorter than my name!
開演前から気づいたと思うけど...
As you might have noticed before the show started...
DJ！
DJ!
最高！
Awesome!
落ちないようにね！本当だよ！
Don't fall! Seriously!
怖そう！絶対！
Looks scary! Definitely!
あそこ超高いぜ！
It's super high up there!
というわけで、ここから先は本当の任務に入っていくぞー！
So then, from here on, we're going into our real mission!
なんですけど... ここで... 「嫌だー！」
However... right here... "No way!"
それは聞かないと... 悲しい...
We have to listen to that... Sad...
ちょっと私から言うのもあれなんで、こよさん！「おいおいおい！」人の口を借りるな！
It's a bit awkward coming from me, so Koyo-san! "Hey hey hey!" Don't use someone else's voice!
はい、ではちょっと大事なお知らせです！
Alright, here is an important announcement!
YouTube、TikTok Liveでご覧になっている方！
Those watching on YouTube and TikTok Live!
無料チラ見せはここまでとなります！
The free preview ends here!
関係ないのに「えー」って言ってくれてる！見れるのにね！
People who aren't even affected are saying "Eh~"! Even though they can still watch!
ですが！この後も生パフォーマンスやゴージャスな楽曲など！
However! After this, there will be live performances and gorgeous songs!
今からでも間に合いますので、この辺！概要欄から、この辺！配信チケットを購入してください！
It's not too late, so around here! From the description box, around here! Please purchase the streaming ticket!
ここ！ここ！ここです！
Here! Here! Right here!
お前ら、絶対買えよな！買った音した！買わないとヤバいよ！
You guys better buy it! I heard the purchase sound! You gotta buy it!
そしてこのライブの感想などはですね、ハッシュタグ #SsoholoX世界リペイント計画 でポストしてくださいね！
And for your thoughts on this concert, please post with the hashtag #SsoholoX世界リペイント計画!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
そしてそして！配信組はいっぱいスクショ撮ってアップしてね！
And also! Streaming viewers, take lots of screenshots and upload them!
お願いしまーす！盛り上がってねー！
Please! Enjoy the show!
はい！ということで
Alright! So...
じゃあ ここからね さっき言ってた通り 本当のミッション始まりますね！
Well then, from here on out, just as we said, the real mission begins!
はい！
Yes!
おい！まだ声出せるの？！
Hey! Can you still make some noise?!
いいよー！
That's awesome!
最高です！
It's the best!
ここにいる全員、そして配信のみんな！覚悟はいいかー！
Everyone here, and everyone on stream! Are you ready?!
ファーストミッション！ここからが本番だー！
First Mission! This is where the real show starts!
それでは、任務続行！
Well then, mission continuation!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[On-Screen Text: The free preview part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!]
無料パートは終了いたしました！ ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!